We're going to be creating a primary partition using the diskpad in the command prompt.
So, here if I go to disk monitor, you can see I have several disk which are offline at the moment.
So, if you open the command prompt as an administrator, and then we enter the following
let me just enter the following diskpad and hit enter, here you can see it's going to take
me to diskpad with diskpad which you can actually use to format, at all it creates a partition
and bring the disk on line.
So, if for example, I enter the following command list disk, here you can see it's going
to show me the disk which are online and the ones that are offline.
At this moment you can see we have only one disk line, and we have several that disk which
are offline, and you can see that this guy from 0, 1, 2 and here you can see till about 6.
So, let's say we want to actually now walk with a phase disk and let me just enter the following
command, select disk 1, and now you can see that this one is now selected.
So, what we need to do right now to bring that disk on line, we just need to enter online disk.
And you see here you can see that this successfully, this path successfully online is selected,
this column just hits list disk, here we go, you can now see that the disk 1 is now online.
So, what you want to actually do again is the following, for example the disk which we have
to walk with a disk 1, so if I just do claim, so what happens is the following is going
to take claim, this is going to erase all the information in that disk, if I do enter
languages to the following list partition, at this moment you can see this demo partition
on this disk to show, so what you want to do right now is the following, I am going to enter
the following, create partition from area, I need to enter, this path hasn't, can I
add the middle, it's right protected, see the system, it won't allow for more information,
so that, I am going to say we just can't add the list, try the following again, create partition
in primary, and here you can see this disk, so see that in creating this petrified partition,
what I actually did, totally saw this problem is the following, I enter the following command
which is attributes, then this clear, read only, so this command will actually credit
disk, not to be read only, and we actually created the protection on that disk, which
allow me now to create the primary partition on that disk, so if we now decided to just
enter the following list partition, let me see if I enter the correct, and then you can
see this partition of one primary, nine gigabytes, and as this disk, you can see that
this just changed, this one just changed to, which is 10 gigabyte to a primary partition,
so that is how you use this path to actually create a primary partition.